culturewhiz.org 2017-06-05

# Privacy Policy | Culture Whiz

**How we secure your personal data at Culture Whiz**

Culture Whiz knows that everyone cares how information about them is used and shared. We aim to uphold the highest standards in security and care to ensure that your trust in us is deserved. This notice describes our policies and by visiting [www.culturewhiz.org](http://www.culturewhiz.org/) you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this notice.

Any personal information provided or to be gathered at [www.culturewhiz.org](http://www.culturewhiz.org/) is controlled by Culture Whiz, Inc. In accordance with the Spanish Data Protection Act 15/1999 of 13 December and other applicable laws, all End Users and Clients have the right to access, rectify and cancel their personal data registered in our commercial database, which has been duly entered in the Spanish Data Protection Register (Nº 20625001445).

As a general rule, we aim to conform fully to the principles laid out in the European Union’s directives on Data Protection. These include the principles of 'Safe Harbor' which mean we may store data on servers located in the United States of America, while ensuring the same standards of data protection that are required within the European Union.

**Why do we collect information and what do we use it for?**

The information we gather from customers helps improve our services for everyone. We use the information to handle orders, deliver products and services, process payments, communicate with you about orders, products, services and promotional offers, update our records and generally maintain your accounts with us. We also use this information to improve our services, prevent or detect fraud or abuses of our website and enable third parties to carry out technical, logistical or other functions on our behalf.

**Here are the types of information we gather.**

Information you give us: We receive and store any information you enter on our website or give us in any other way.  
Automatic information: We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many websites, we use "cookies" and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses [www.culturewhiz.org](http://www.culturewhiz.org/)  
Third party information: We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

**Does Culture Whiz share my personal information?**

We do not share information about you with any third party; however, we may send you information about products and services that we think might interest you. We do not give any of your personal information to any third-parties. If you do not wish to receive any newsletters or other promotional email from us all you need to do is adjust your email preference in the Account Management area on the website.

**How secure is my information?**

We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input. Credit and debit card payments are verified through our bank, Caixa Catalunya ([www.caixacatalunya.es](http://www.caixacatalunya.es/)). We do not maintain records of any credit or debit card data on our website. We reveal only the last digits of your credit card number when confirming an order. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards in connection with the collection, storage and disclosure of personally identifiable customer information. Our security procedures mean that we may occasionally request proof of identity before we disclose personal information to you. It is important for you to protect against unauthorised access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when you finish using a shared computer.

**Can I see what information you have about me?**

You can see all information we hold by logging in and looking at the information in your account areas, with the exception of some automatically generated information that is associated with your account for the prevention of fraud.

**Conditions of Use, Notices and Revisions**

If you have any concern about privacy at Culture Whiz, please send a thorough description by email or by post and we will try to resolve it as quickly as possible. Contact details below.

Our business changes constantly and this Privacy Notice will also change. When a change occurs we may email you with details, unless you have instructed us not to, but you should check our website frequently to see recent changes. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Notice applies to all information that we have about you and your account. We stand behind the promises we make, however, and will never materially change our policies and practices to make them less protective of customer information collected in the past without the consent of affected customers.
